

# **Gonzalo, TERZANO**

Web Developer
26 Years
Córdoba, Argentina
Mobile: +549 0264 154649709
E-mail: gonzaloterzano@gmail.com

### PERSONAL STATEMENT

Hello! My name is Gonzalo Terzano. I am a Semi-Senior Web Developer, with 2-3 years of experience in the area. I have many skills to work as a team member and also individually. I always push myself to the limit in order to achieve excellece in my work.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

February 2016 – Present Globant Cordoba, Argentina

**Position:** Web UI Developer

Working in a busy team sometimes under pressure. Always making projects of eLearning, mostly using AngularJS, but also creating friendly & interactive environments with HTML5 and Phaser (JS Framework).

April 2015 – January 2016 TravelPAQ San Juan, Argentina

**Position:** Web UI Developer & Backend Developer

I worked in a startup focused on improve relationships between tourism companies. This was an exciting experience where I learned a lot of new and different technologies.

April 2010 – January 2016 UNSJ, FCEFyN San Juan, Argentina

**Position:** Teaching assistant

Worked in six different subjects, assisting in practical classes, even giving class in some particular cases.

# **SKILLS**

- ✓ AngularJS
- ✓ JQuery
- ✓ JavaScript
- ✓ KnockoutJS
- ✓ HTML5
- ✓ CSS3

- ✓ Bootstrap
- ✓ CakePHP
- ✓ Git
- ✓ Gulp
- ✓ NodeJS
- ✓ PHP

- ✓ C#
- ✓ C
- ✓ SourceTree
- ✓ Photoshop

# **EDUCATION**

2009 - Present San Juan - Argentina

"Degree in Computer Science"

UNSJ – Fac. Cs. Exactas F. y N., without

preseting the Thesis.

GPA: 8.6 of 10

2005 - 2008 San Juan - Argentina "Electronics Technician"

UNSJ - Esc Industrial D. F. Sarmiento

GPA: 8.57 of 10

# **LENGUAGES**

**Spanish:** Native

English: Conversational level